Guide to the National Education Association-Conventions records, 1857-1998 NEA1008.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Conventions and Conferences, Bulk, 1970-1996 1858-1998; 1970-1996; Series 1; National Education Association of the United States. Meeting.; 85 Linear Feet
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Candidates, Series 1 (Box 1405, Folder 9)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Candidates-Elections, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Candidates-Voting, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Car Rental, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 3)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Caucuses, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 4)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Caucuses-State, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Childcare, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 6)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Contract Dispute, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 7)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Convention-Board/Promo, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 8)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Convention-Contracts, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 9)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Convention Hall-Correspondence, 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 10)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Convention Schedule, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 11)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Correspondence-Director/OCCM, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 12)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 13)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Delegate Material Mailings, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 14)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Delegate Seating, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 15)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Demonstrations, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 16)
    Contains 11 photos and 1 button.
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Drivers, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 17)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Evaluation, Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 18)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Exhibits [file 1/6], 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 1406, Folder 19)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Exhibits [file 2/6], 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 1407, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Exhibits [file 3/6], 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 1407, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Exhibits [file 4/6], 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 1407, Folder 3)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Exhibits [file 5/6], 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 1407, Folder 4)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Exhibits [file 6/6], 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 1407, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Fire Safety, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1407, Folder 6)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-First Aid, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1407, Folder 7)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Floor Plans, Series 1 (Box 1407, Folder 8)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Floor Privilege/Ribbon Guide, Series 1 (Box 1407, Folder 9)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Food Service, Series 1 (Box 1408, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Friendship Night, Series 1 (Box 1408, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Furniture and Equipment Orders, Series 1 (Box 1408, Folder 3)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Handouts [file 1/3], Series 1 (Box 1408, Folder 4)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Handouts [file 2/3], Series 1 (Box 1408, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Handouts [file 3/3], Series 1 (Box 1408, Folder 6)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Host Committee [file 1/3], Series 1 (Box 1408, Folder 7)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Host Committee [file 2/3], Series 1 (Box 1409, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Host Committee [file 3/3], Series 1 (Box 1409, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Host Committments, Series 1 (Box 1409, Folder 3)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Airport Hilton and Towers, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1409, Folder 4)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Airport Marriot, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1409, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Ambassador Hotel, Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-AMFAC Hotel, Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Best Western Inn Towne, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 3)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Biltmore Hotel, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 4)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Century Plaza Hotel, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Embassy Hotel, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 6)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Figueroa Hotel, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 7)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-General [file 1/3], 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 8)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-General [file 2/3], 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 9)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-General [file 3/3], 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1410, Folder 10)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Hacienda Hotel at LAX, Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Hilton, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Convention Center, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 3)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Downtown, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 4)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Hyatt at LAX, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Hyatt Regency, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 6)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Hyatt Wilshire Hotel, Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 7)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Marina Beach Hotel, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 8)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Marina Del Ray, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 9)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Mayfair, Series 1 (Box 1411, Folder 10)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-New Ontani Hotel and Gardens, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Pickups, Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Sheraton Grande Hotel, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 3)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Sheraton Plaza La Renta, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 4)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Sheraton Town House, 1985; Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Sheraton Universal, Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 6)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Stouffers Concourse Hotel, 1985-1987; Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 7)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-University Hilton, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 8)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Viscount, Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 9)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Hotels-Westin-Bonaventure, 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1412, Folder 10)
  - 1987- Los Angeles, CA- Invest in America: Support Public Education- 125th Annual Meeting, June 30- July 5, 1987; Series 1 (Box 4631, Folder 18)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Magazine, Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Miscellaneous, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-NEA-PAC Giveaway, Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 3)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Non-Profit Affiliate Fundraiser, Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 4)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Physically Handicapped, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 5)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Program/Platform Guests, Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 6)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Program Distribution, 1985-1986; Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 7)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Programs, Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 8)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Restaurant Survey, Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 9)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Sales Tax, Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 10)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Staff Dates/Staff Housing, Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 11)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-State Coordinators [file 1/2], 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1413, Folder 12)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-State Coordinators [file 2/2], 1986-1987; Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 1)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-Transportation-Tours, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 2)
  - 1987-Los Angeles, CA-VIPs, Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Bills, Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Budget, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Busing, Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 6)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Camping, Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 7)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Candidates, Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 8)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Car Rental, Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 9)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Caucuses, Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 10)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Childcare, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 11)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Convention Bureau [file 1/2], 1976-1988; Series 1 (Box 1414, Folder 12)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Convention Bureau [file 2/2], 1976-1988; Series 1 (Box 1415, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Convention Bureau-Promotional, Series 1 (Box 1415, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Convention Bureau-Contracts, Series 1 (Box 1415, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Convention Bureau-Correspondence, 1986-1989; Series 1 (Box 1415, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Convention Schedule, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1415, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Correspondence, 1984-1986; Series 1 (Box 1415, Folder 6)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Delegate Material Mailings, Series 1 (Box 1415, Folder 7)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Delegate Materials-Representative Assembly, Series 1 (Box 1415, Folder 8)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Demonstrations, Series 1 (Box 1415, Folder 9)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Drivers, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 1416, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Exhibits [file 1/4], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1416, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Exhibits [file 2/4], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1416, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Exhibits [file 3/4], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1416, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Exhibits [file 4/4], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1416, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Facilities Contract, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1416, Folder 6)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-First Aid, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1416, Folder 7)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Floor Plans, Series 1 (Box 1417, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Food Service, Series 1 (Box 1417, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Friendship Night, Series 1 (Box 1417, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Host Committee, Series 1 (Box 1417, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Host Committee Manual, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1417, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Bienville House, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1417, Folder 6)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Clarion, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1417, Folder 7)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Committments, 1987; Series 1 (Box 1417, Folder 8)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Committment Form, Series 1 (Box 1418, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-De La Poste, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1418, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Doubletree, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1418, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Fairmont, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1418, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-General, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1418, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Holiday Inn Crowne Plaza, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1418, Folder 6)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Hyatt Regency [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1419, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Hyatt Regency [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1419, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Inter Continental, Series 1 (Box 1419, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Le Meridien, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1419, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Marriot [file 1/2], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1419, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Marriot [file 2/2], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1420, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Monteleone, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1420, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-New Orleans Hilton, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1420, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Radisson Suite, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1420, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Royal Sonesta [file 1/2], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1423, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Royal Sonesta [file 2/2], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1423, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Sheraton, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1423, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Hotels-Westin Canal Plaza, 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1423, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Housing, Series 1 (Box 1423, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA- Insure America's Future: Invest in Public Education- 126th Annual Meeting, July 2-7, 1988; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Joint Conference, Series 1 (Box 1423, Folder 6)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Magazine, Series 1 (Box 1423, Folder 7)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Miscellaneous, 1985-1988; Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Non-Profit Fundraisers, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Physically Disabled, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-PAC Giveaway, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Prizes, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Program, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 6)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Program/Project Guests, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 7)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Reports [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 8)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Reports [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 9)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Restaurant Survey, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 10)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Ribbons, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 11)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Roll Calls, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 12)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Security, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 13)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Speeches, Series 1 (Box 1424, Folder 14)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Staff, Series 1 (Box 1425, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-State Coordinators [file 1/4], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1425, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-State Coordinators [file 2/4], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1425, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-State Coordinators [file 3/4], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1425, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-State Coordinators [file 4/4], 1987-1988; Series 1 (Box 1425, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-State Housing List, Series 1 (Box 1425, Folder 6)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Superdome Contract, Series 1 (Box 1426, Folder 1)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Telephone Directory, Series 1 (Box 1426, Folder 2)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-TV Communications, Series 1 (Box 1426, Folder 3)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Tourist and Convention Commission, 1986-1988; Series 1 (Box 1426, Folder 4)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-Tours/Transport, Series 1 (Box 1426, Folder 5)
  - 1988-New Orleans, LA-VIPs, Series 1 (Box 1426, Folder 6)
  - 1989-Washington, DC-Bills, Series 1 (Box 1426, Folder 7)
  - 1989-Washington, DC-Convention and Visitors Association [file 1/2], 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 1426, Folder 8)
  - 1989-Washington, DC-Convention and Visitors Association [file 2/2], 1984-1988; Series 1 (Box 1426, Folder 9)
  - 1989-Washington, DC-Program/Platform Guests, Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Adjustments, Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Atwood, Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Budget, Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Busing, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Camping, Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Candidates, Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Car Rental, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Caucuses-Minority, 1985-1990; Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 9)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Childcare, Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 10)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Contracts, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 11)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Convention Bureau-Correspondence, 1987-1990; Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 12)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Convention Bureau-Promotional [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1427, Folder 13)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Convention Bureau-Promotional [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1428, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Convention Hall-Contracts, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1428, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Convention Hall-Correspondence, 1987-1989; Series 1 (Box 1428, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Delegate Handouts [file 1/4], Series 1 (Box 1428, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Delegate Handouts [file 2/4], Series 1 (Box 1428, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Delegate Handouts [file 3/4], Series 1 (Box 1428, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Delegate Handouts [file 4/4], Series 1 (Box 1428, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Delegate Material-Mailing, Series 1 (Box 1429, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Delegate Material-Representative Assembly, Series 1 (Box 1429, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Delegate Seating, Series 1 (Box 1429, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Demonstrations/Protests, Series 1 (Box 1429, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Drivers [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1429, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Drivers [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1429, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Evaluation, Series 1 (Box 1429, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Exhibits [file 1/4], Series 1 (Box 1429, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Exhibits [file 2/4], Series 1 (Box 1429, Folder 9)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Exhibits [file 3/4], Series 1 (Box 1430, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Exhibits [file 4/4], Series 1 (Box 1430, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Floor Plans, Series 1 (Box 1430, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Food Service, Series 1 (Box 1430, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Freight, Series 1 (Box 1430, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Friendship Night, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1430, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Furniture, 1990-1991; Series 1 (Box 1430, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Host Committee [file 1/3], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1431, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Host Committee [file 2/3], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1431, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Host Committee [file 3/3], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1431, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Adams Mark Hotel, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1431, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Allis Plaza Hotel, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1431, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Americana Hotel, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1431, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Best Western-Overland Park, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1431, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Best Western-Seville Plaza, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1431, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Club House Inn, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1431, Folder 9)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Comfort Inn-Northeast, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Comfort Inn-Westport, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Committments, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Country Inn KCI, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Days Inn KCI, Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Doubletree, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Drury Inn, Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Embassy on the Park, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Embassy Suites, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 9)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Embassy Suites-Country Club, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 10)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Embassy Suites-Overland Park, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1432, Folder 11)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-General [file 1/3], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1433, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-General [file 2/3], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1433, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-General [file 3/3], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1433, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Hampton Inn, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1433, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Hilton Airport, Series 1 (Box 1433, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Hilton Plaza Inn, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1433, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Historic Suites, Series 1 (Box 1433, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Holiday Inn, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1433, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Downtown, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1433, Folder 9)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Lenexa, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Mission Overland Park, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Holiday Inn-Sports Complex, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Howard Johnson-Central, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Howard Johnson-East, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Howard Johnson-Lenexa, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Hyatt Regency, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Hyatt Regency Crown Center, 1988-1989; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-La Quinta Motor Inn, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 9)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Marriot, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 10)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Marriot-Courtyard, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 11)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Marriot-Overland Park, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1434, Folder 12)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Marriot Plaza-Kansas City, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1435, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Not Using, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1435, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Park Place, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1435, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Quarterage at Westport, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1435, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Radisson Suite, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1435, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Ramada, 1989; Series 1 (Box 1435, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Ramada-Airport, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1435, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Ramada-North, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1435, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Ramada-Southwest, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1436, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Raphael Hotel, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1436, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Ritz-Carlton, Series 1 (Box 1436, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Rodeway Inn-Downtown, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1436, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Rodeway Inn-Overland, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1436, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Sheraton, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1436, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Hotels-Westin Crown Center, Series 1 (Box 1436, Folder 7)
  - 1990- Kansas City, MO- It's Time for Action- 128th Annual Meeting, July 3-8, 1990; Series 1 (Box 4632, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Joint Conference, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1436, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Magazine, 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1437, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Magazine [file 1/3], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1440, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Magazine [file 2/3], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1440, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Magazine [file 3/3], 1989-1990; Series 1 (Box 1440, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Miscellaneous, 1988-1990; Series 1 (Box 1437, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-New Business Items, Series 1 (Box 1437, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Non-Profit Fundraising [file 1/2], Series 1 (Box 1437, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Non-Profit Fundraising [file 2/2], Series 1 (Box 1437, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Physically Challenged, Series 1 (Box 1437, Folder 6)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Printing, Series 1 (Box 1437, Folder 7)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Program, Series 1 (Box 1437, Folder 8)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Program/Platform Guests, Series 1 (Box 1438, Folder 1)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-"RA Today", Series 1 (Box 1438, Folder 2)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Restaurant Survey, Series 1 (Box 1438, Folder 3)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Ribbons, Series 1 (Box 1438, Folder 4)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Site Inspection Report, 1986; Series 1 (Box 1438, Folder 5)
  - 1990-Kansas City, MO-Staff Travel, Series 1 (Box 1438, Folder 6)